Hey,
hey,
hey.
Uh hello everyone.
A warm good evening to all. Hello.
Hello.
Good evening. D good evening.
How's everyone doing tonight? Today.
Hello Solar. Welcome. Welcome.
Hello. Good evening.
Oh boy, I feel a bit tired. I was
supposed to start the stream
earlier in the morning,
but I thought of streaming in the
evening at 4:00 p.m.
I was like working on some stream stuff
like a like the back end stuff. Then I
felt so tired. I I wanted to sleep but I
like take a nap and late late night
stream.
But as
4:36 a.m. Oh, no.
Yeah, it's really late for you.
Wow. Damn.
You're It's really late for you.
Crazy.
Um
All right. Um, yeah, today we'll be
doing arc as usual.
You could expect me to do a lot of arc
arc raider stream cuz this is a fun game
honestly. Yeah.
Anyway, uh let me check some stuff.
Wait, some of my stuff is broken. Oh my
god. Crazy.
Okay, I will
close this.
Okay.
All right.
Let's go. Arish time.
My busy is really suffering right now.
Ah, this sucks.
A question. Go ahead.
Go ahead.
All right.
Raiders,
not enough space. Oh my god. Will we
ever do another Joathon stream?
Not sure. That's a good question, but I
am not
sure I will do that again.
I would like to, but I don't think I can
physically ever do that that much.
[snorts]
Yeah, I I don't think I could. Uh
So, I don't know if I could honestly
cuz now next year, next month um
next April onwards, I'll be in Japan
now. So, I won't be able to do streams
and everything
and everything for a while till I get
settled. If I'm there and stuff for an
year or two or maybe perhaps 2, 3 years,
I won't be able to do like longer than
2our streams
cuz I have to balance IRL,
part-time, this and that, life this and
that. Uh so it depends if I am able to
stream even. So of course I can do
another joathon thingy but what's the
point of doing another joathon if
there's no specific goal for it? No.
Think about it like that.
Last time I did joathon just for the
model. That's for money and everything.
That didn't go well. I didn't have
anything new and everything.
I somehow winged it and that's about it,
right?
Uh
yeah, like or of course I could also do
another way that is
do like a goal for a specific number of
followers or something.
uh specific number of followers or
something like for example
uh not on YouTube more most probably
Twitch maybe like thousand followers on
Twitch kind of goal at least do an end
to end stream till we hit thousand
followers or something
that work [laughter]
yeah we're already 1,000 follow
subscribers on YouTube now for Twitch
Twitch is like how much I forgot.
I think
I think Twitch is like 800 700. No, we
could try to grind to be able to
get up to,000. That that that's a good
goal, I guess.
I wouldn't mind doing that. Seems like a
good goal. You got V views though? Yeah,
I think I did. But because of the
incident which happened
on August, I lost half of everyone,
right? So it's pro it's more of a
restart, right?
It's more of a restart, right? All the
viewers I ever had left. Now it's more
like I have to build my audience from
the ground up, right? After what drama
happened and everything.
Uh, so
yeah. Oh, there there's that too. Yeah,
I'm 745
followers. Not Twitch wise. I was
thinking we can do a,000 follower end
stream on Twitch after January.
Um,
after January, that's better. I feel
like that I always wanted to equalize
now. I feel like that will be a good
opportunity.
So,
what about kick? What about kick?
Kick as well. Kick. I'm like I have
[music] 202 followers on kick. What?
What? What?
What?
Crazy.
Yeah, people actually follow me on kick.
What?
Crazy. I never knew. What?
That's really nice. They actually know.
That's really nice.
Yeah. Anyhow, um, what was I doing?
Guess it was kind of like a downloading
Twitch. You don't have to download
Twitch, honestly. Twitch has ads. No,
Twitch has ads and everything. So,
it's all good. You can be a YouTube
uh memberish.
Too bad I'm following
Yeah, whatever you feel like doing. All
good. All good.
[snorts] All good.
One shotgun.
Okay, I'll keep this in the background.
Okay, I'll keep it in the background and
we'll start the game. All right.
I never made a Twitch account. Oh.
Oh god. I mean, Twitch is mainly for
watching live streams, right?
So, there's that
rocket. Okay.
Yeah, there's a new uh creator deck
which came out.
I would like to get this outfit.
Seems nice.
I would love to get the blue one.
Blue is better.
I mean, I like the current one.
This makes me feel more
h
wiser.
Rest back.
>> [snorts]
>> Yeah, I like this blue one.
Okay, let's uh play with this.
I do see a stream if I had I never had
account. You can go twitch.tv/talknext.
You can still watch it without an
account.
I can still watch it without an account.
It should work.
Do you see it?
Over.
Da da da da da da da da da.
I think I can sell this.
How do I verify? Uh, you verify with
your email address.
You have to just
verify your email it is. Hello RB.
Hello. Hello. Welcome.
Yes. [laughter]
You should play this game. It's really
fun.
Hello.
Uh, I have a Pilgrim Peak security key.
I could go to the Pilgrim Peak.
Uh, what do I do?
Merry Christmas. Merry Christmas to you
as well. Hey, talk. All right, D. No
worries.
Okay. Uh,
should I
Okay, we'll go do the trials. Okay,
I'll put it in my safe pocket.
And uh
we'll take shields.
Repair our shields.
We'll take uh
uh we'll take uh this looting argument.
I mean, wait.
More quick slot uses. No, no, no way.
Tactical. This is better. No, slightly
lower looting. Yeah. Yeah, this is
better. Tactical one.
So, we will take an arpeggio. We have so
many arpeggios and uh heavy hitting
weapon.
So, medium and heavy ammo. Heavy.
Medium.
But should I take the shotgun? Do I have
shotgun? I have only two
ammo is weak. Okay, we'll use the
pharaoh.
No money. Yeah,
I'm broke though. I only I need to get
to 5 million be before the next
expedition which is
which is 56 days from now.
So they this game has like that reset
thingy. It's optional. So you can do the
expedition. So it's a complete wipe of
your character. The benefits will be you
get skill points.
You get five extra skill points per
minute.
Uh check Twitch real quick. What's
happening on Twitch?
I am see reading Twitch.
Uh then yeah, there's buff and stuff. We
have to do the expedition.
Really nice.
What is this?
Oh, this thing. The Lizzy.
Oh, nice. Nice. I had the snow. I'll put
the Lizzy this time.
>> Okay.
Uh,
one second.
All my sevens went to Space Marines.
Wait, I heard of that game.
Space Marines, too. I heard of this. Oh,
Warhammer. Oh.
Oh, nice.
Ah,
Warhammer.
Uh solar you can just verify your email
and just wait for a while few days or
something. I forgot my Twitch Twitch
verification thingy. But
it's not required that you need to
verify your phone number. So don't worry
too much about it.
Uh okay. I need to check the interactive
map. Dark raiders
direct him up for where will be the
spawn for the
uh leaper the jumpy guy. So we are try
we will try to kill the leaper twice.
Okay it will be in here.
So leaper spawns over here and over
here.
This and this. This and this. So, we
come to launch tower. No, arrival
building or here.
I think it's best if I go to arrival
building. Take cover over here. Don't
want the spider, big spider to come
here. It'll be locked. It couldn't jump
in a closed space. Right. Then I throw
the gas uh trailblazer grenade. Kill it
in one go. Wait 8 minutes till it
respawns and do this again and my trials
will be over.
I think that is a good idea.
Yeah, we need to get to the purple
reward.
I just need to kill it twice and I'm
good. Yeah, just need to kill it twice
and I'm good. Good.
Yeah. So, uh, we need we will need a lot
of grenades.
Grenades. I don't want to use these.
These are for the big boys, the queen
and the matriarch.
Uh, yeah, we can take these.
Let's hope I do not die. Take a lot of
bandage. We I should not die this time.
A lot of heals. A lot of bandages.
Adrenaline is needed.
I take as much as uh bandages as I can.
Uh shield recharger. I don't have it or
something. What? Where is it?
Shield recharger.
Uh where is it?
What? I don't have it. What?
My mom was missing all this stuff.
[laughter]
Hey,
I don't need to murder too much.
>> Oh god.
I shield.
I could spend money though. But should
I?
Okay, it's 1,000
>> about roller skating. It's expensive.
>> I shouldn't have sold my power cell,
man. Okay, fine. I'll I'll buy it for
him.
>> Hello again.
>> I do so love money.
>> I will need to loot stuff and get my
money back.
Okay. For extra.
Yep. Yep. Yep. I I'm like double
thinking. Should I I would like to have
extra. Ah, it's fine. One safe poker is
enough now. I don't need the core
anyways.
Okay. Uh, heavy ammo. Don't forget.
Okay, we got one stack. Oh boy.
Okay, this should be enough. Hi,
Alex. Let's do our best. Wait, wait,
wait. Grenades. Grenades. You forgot.
You forgot. You forgot.
Take as many ass grenades as you can.
Uh cute.
Okay, this should be good enough. Uh
actually we will split it into two.
All right,
we will not waste Wait, wait, wait.
You know what? Split it. Wait. I'll keep
one in my little stash and keep take
two. If anything bad happens,
I'll use this snap blast.
Yeah,
I was a moderator in the stream. Oh,
that was experience.
Okay, let's go. Oh, wait.
Stop. Stop. Stop. We have to upgrade our
stuff. I'll have to take a good
Yeah, if you feel like sharing, feel
free to. All good.
Okay, let's go.
Let's go.
Please spawn me on top east. Top east,
please.
Top east or west? I'll just find the
leaper, kill it,
call it the day, and exit. Leave it.
Leave.
I have to strategize this time better.
Gotta do my best.
>> Okay, this is not not bad. Not bad of a
spawn. Okay, we have to go here.
>> LET'S GO TO THAT LOCATION.
>> It's a it's a clean spawn. It's a fresh
raid. Okay.
>> Did you bring those grenades?
>> Oh, nice.
But I'll need someone to chuck the
>> spammer feared me.
>> Wow. Nice.
I forgot to take ad uh
adrenaline with me.
That's fine.
Feel the bottled across them ago, I
guess. Not sure. No, it's fine. It's
fine.
Chatted like a hawk.
Yeah, you do chat a lot. That's a good
thing, you know.
>> HEY, DON'T SHOOT.
>> All right.
Okay, we just need to kill the leaper
and then come back here and loot so we
have time
Go.
You know, a goldfish has a spam of 5
months or 1 year. I thought goldfish has
a memory of 10 minutes or something.
My game is crashing. What the heck?
Why? Why? Why? Why? Don't do this to me.
Someone's killing something.
Wait, it's someone hitting killing the
>> Don't shoot.
>> Hey,
>> don't shoot.
HEY.
>> OH, go go go go go. It's here. It's
here. Kill it.
Oh [\h__\h] Oh no.
Oh my god. Okay. Rest. Rest.
I hate the lag. I hate the lag. What is
happening?
Okay, we call out the
thing.
Let it come.
Let it come. Let it come.
Oh sh Oh my god.
Now the question is
I hate this.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Hold, hold.
I hate the space. They stop lagging.
Ah, enemy. Why are you here?
Oh my god.
I need a This is bad spot. This is a bad
spot. Next
Oh my lord. Holy.
[\h__\h]
Help. Help. Help. Help. Help. Help.
Help.
Please help.
Could you revive, please? I'm trying to
do the challenge.
He doesn't have it. [laughter]
Uh def. Do you have a def
Please don't kill. Please. Please.
Uh could you guide me to the extract,
please?
I have nothing. Please.
[laughter]
I hate life.
Thank you.
How far is the extract?
Why this play uh person is helping me so
much.
H. Do you have a bandage?
>> Appreciate it.
Ah,
how far
[laughter]
I'm I don't think I'll survive. You can
take my loot. I have a trailblazer if
you want.
>> [laughter and gasps]
>> It's the second time I s I am
struggling.
[laughter]
I took my good gun. Why lord?
I took so many grenades. I took so many
good things. Everything I had.
Who was this person? Thank you.
At least I have one. [laughter]
Did you see the lag, man? The lag.
Second time this happened. This is the
second time it happened.
The roll.
I I'm starting to hate the game now.
If I had teammate then okay, I would
have been saved. But
I can't buy trail blazer anymore.
>> You're starting to make this place look
busy.
>> Hope you've got room in your pack for
that.
>> I lost the trailer.
It's fine. It's fine. It's fine. It's
fine. Um,
uh,
I don't have an anvil, so I'll go a
rattler.
Oh my god,
probably tea, I guess.
probably for tea.
>> I know your face.
I'll only use that.
I I lost my flame spray.
I might have to give up on this.
I am so poor, man.
I'm so poor. I don't have money. Oh, why
am I so poor?
Wow.
Oh, I took every Oh, no. I took all of
my shield recharges
and my herbal bandage too.
Bro, I'm so broke.
I am so Okay, you know what? I'll spend
money. It's fine. Okay, I'll get No, no,
no. Bandages are expensive. I'll get
this
probably. This is expensive.
I'm going to burn out my
>> sure should be just the thing for you.
Ah,
>> this is bad. That's a dumb move. Ah,
it's okay. It's okay. It's okay.
This time I'm sure I will not fail.
Let's hope.
>> Okay.
>> Oh, where's the space for lunch? M.
Okay.
Oh, wait, wait, wait. I need ad drill
in.
Ah, I'm so broke.
Forgot something.
>> Better than a cup of coffee. Not that I
would know.
I spent 80,000
getting gear uh weapons and grenades and
stuff. Oh,
[laughter]
please do not die easily. Jo,
I beg you. I cry now.
Everything is in the low setting.
Spend 80,000.
Charging capital discharge in 5 seconds.
Okay, let's go. Don't worry, the money
we spend will make it back. We'll just
uh go for a raid and then loot up good
items and we'll be good.
I can make it back again.
As long as this as long Oh my god, my PC
is struggling. As long as my P um as
long as I do not have any issues
as in
my game freezing and stuff like what
happened earlier. No, game froze
and I died. We don't want that.
I really don't want that.
>> Let's go to that location.
>> Oh, it's a late raid. Should I reset?
I mean, it's a late confirming your
request.
Should I reset?
>> It's a late raid though. What's the
point
coming in a really late raid? You know
what? Let's reset actually
before we reset. Uh, I'll just loot some
stuff. Get make my money back.
Don't shoot.
>> It seems none of these places is looted
yet, which is nice. Good for us.
Oh, nice.
Oh, nice. Nice.
Wait,
someone's here.
29,000. Okay.
>> Hey, don't shoot.
>> I got scared, bro. Is that a rat? It
just went inside.
I have a question. Hello.
>> Hey, Raider.
>> Yes. Go ahead. What's your question?
Oh, look. Another rat.
What inspired you to be a creator?
H,
that's a good question.
Huh? I I think I mainly wanted to be a
musician
first
and live streamer. Secondly,
I would say like I got inspired by
seeing other creatives make stuff and
everything.
I I was like I also want to do something
like this,
see how it goes and everything.
Yeah, that's how I started.
Actually,
I mainly wanted to try something out,
figure out my stuff.
Like, I had a lot of bunch of
uh I had a bunch of hobbies.
I was like, I want to try doing chasing
my dreams and my hobbies.
Hence, yeah, as long as I'm having fun,
it's all good.
If I'm not having fun, then what's the
point of this, right?
Famous. Nah, I'm not famous.
Nope. Nope.
I don't see myself as famous as they
electrical components. I needed this.
Is no.
If you're looking at the subscriber
count and stuff, that doesn't matter
much.
What matters is the amount of people who
come by to streams and all those
matters. Numbers doesn't matter much. I
don't want to look at the numbers too
much.
So
I still feel like I'm nobody.
I just exist in my own space. Just doing
what I love doing. That's it.
That's all.
But as a creator, I feel like I'm not
doing much as a creator. I feel like I
have a lot of room of improvement. Room
for improvement.
I want to turn my streams into like a
show kind of thingy where people come by
they
feel like they're in the moment or
something and memorable moment they will
never forget kind of thing. Every stream
being like a memorable moment kind of
thingy. I would like to do that one day.
in it.
>> Head home at the central elevator.
>> That'll be super nice.
>> Let's head home at the west elevator.
>> But for that I need to
have good equipment this and that.
Could you repeat that? Oh uh I meant
like I want if like
YouTube it's okay. I know what it is. I
meant like um
I meant like I'm not good as a creator
in in terms of entertaining. That's what
I meant.
And I feel like
I would love to have
my streams
rememberable for those who are coming by
and stuff now. Like they will not forget
they were there in the moment. Kind of
like that.
Uh I like that. Yeah. Yeah. cuz I feel
like honestly I just feel like streaming
and just talking and just yapping like
this isn't much. I want to like do a lot
of crazy stuff, but I'm limited in terms
of equipment and everything. So, I'm
like, man, what do I do?
Show
a good character. A thank you.
[laughter]
I don't know.
I feel like I have a lot of room for
improvement.
I got to put in extra work.
does that too.
And and the thing is I've been doing
this for like how many years now? Six
years now.
And
I I feel like it it I it feel like it's
already past the time where I can see
this as a hobby. I've been doing it as a
hobby. I would like to turn it into a
serious thing, but I'm not sure
>> for that. I have to really really
>> like [laughter]
brainstorm and be smart about how to do
things and everything.
Be more serious serious. I would like to
do that one day though. Not now, I
guess,
cuz next year onwards is going to be
like life arc for me, right? So, this
will be secondary.
But it is fine. As long as I enjoy it,
I'll be fine.
>> Yeah.
res
39K.
Do what works for you. Yep. That's what
I'm going to do.
Yep. Yep. Yep.
Ah, my mother called me. Huh? Wait, wait
one second.
Yeah, I don't know. I have to focus
there.
I'm telling you something that's
happening. I I'm start from the
beginning. Okay. But remember if you're
sharing sharing personal things and
stuff, remember you're talking on a
public space, right? So Adish can also
see it and everything. So be careful
what what you're hyping and this and
that. Okay? I don't I don't mind. But
yeah,
just the disclaimer.
My rain god. What's a rain god?
Rain god.
did not make my money back.
Ah, okay. Okay, that one. Okay, got it.
Got it. Got it. Continue. Continue.
Sorry for interrupting you. Continue.
Yeah, he doesn't know he's paying for
it. Ah, I see.
It's $30. Ah,
for the last one.
H. Not bad of a spawn.
And it's the almost the fresh raid. Not
bad. I can just kill it.
Oh my god.
Only when I stream, I'm feeling fame
drops. Why?
I'm streaming on 720p, too. Is it not
enough for this game? for my PC to
handle this.
Super weird.
Oh no, I'm blocked to my
pay me $60 order buying tape gas and
mail off a package.
Okay,
to breach this
Hey, don't shoot.
>> Hey there.
It's going to have to work. Am
I falling though?
Uh, is it me or is it not here?
I hear it. There you are.
Okay, this
CC see my PC is lagging so much.
What if will it come inside here?
If I lure it.
I feel like this is a risky move. Do not
do this dog.
No, no, no. I'm thinking what if I do it
from here? It won't jump, right?
I swear to God if we die if I die.
Are you sure
there's a bomb rocket here?
Come
on.
Come on.
Heat. Heat.
>> [groaning]
>> Come on. Come on.
Yeah. Yeah. Take care. Take care. Take
care. No worries.
Okay, got it.
Why is this freak here?
Okay, there's so much ammo on this.
Hey, don't shoot.
Heat. Heat.
Oh my lord.
Don't shoot.
>> Why is this freak here?
I'll hide over here.
Okay. [sighs and gasps]
Okay. Uh
does anyone Okay, I'll just watch my own
stream. I need to know the time. Uh,
okay. I didn't know the time.
Uh 15, right? 15
calculator.
15 - 8 7 minutes. Oh, we have to kill it
in seven minutes. Dang it.
Oh boy.
I'm going to extract there.
>> I do not have much stuff on me
as well.
Oh, I can use it this time.
Okay.
Nice.
An Arc Orbiter is on route. The safe
window is closing. You have 10 minutes
to return to Spiranza. I repeat, 10
minutes.
[sighs] Okay.
Uh, seven minutes in there.
Have a few bits of ammo.
I just need a little bit more. That's
it.
Don't try to take on any force.
Bliss is my only chance. I just have to
get it right.
[groaning]
That's the bread horn it.
Okay, it's all wash time.
Find the leaper and we kill it. Okay.
Okay. It's almost time.
Uh it's 8 minute, right? I will just
just wait till 6 minute. Maybe that's
maybe overkill. I I'm not sure.
As long as I can leave with something,
I'm fine. I'm fine if I lose everything.
Okay. It's a minute. It should be up.
I do not see a leaper.
I do not see a leaper
game, please.
[\h__\h]
I [\h__\h] I hate this.
Dang it.
I see the leaper. Okay. I see the
leaper. I see the leaper.
Oh my god.
All raiders, arc on screen. 5 minutes
left. Go find your way home. I receive 5
minutes.
No [\h__\h] help.
Somebody help me, please. Somebody,
anybody, please help. Help. Help. Help.
Help.
Please.
Please,
please help anybody.
Don't shoot. Hey. Hello, Raider. Hey.
Hello.
Please help.
Please help anybody.
Help.
Help me.
Revive me someone.
Okay.
Hey there. Hello, Raider. Hello, Raider.
Hello there.
Hello. Help.
Oh my. What is this freaking ending?
I almost got it.
Why? Why? Why? Why? Why? Why?
Man, what the heck?
[laughter]
I almost finished,
bro.
No. I hate this. I hate this. I
[laughter] hate this.
Why?
I tried, man.
[laughter and cough]
I freaking tried.
I did my best.
>> Well, my favorite repeat customer. Don't
tell the others.
>> I don't have anything else I could use.
>> We've had to build our
We've had to build our top side
infrastructure.
>> [cough]
>> Man, just why am I this unlucky?
Friendly
safely stay alive.
Huh? [sighs and gasps]
Come on man.
Oh,
roof.
I don't even have
[snorts]
steel spring
>> back again.
>> I can't take buy anything now.
Some folks shop quick, some just stay.
I'm fine with either.
>> This is just dumb.
>> Come on in.
We always need more green fingers around
here.
>> You came to the right place.
A part of me really wants to buy the
cracker or renegade or something.
>> No, you can't take any out to the
practice range.
Don't want to spend money, bro.
What if I lose this?
Lever action cowboy style in the right
hands. [clears throat] Very usable.
>> Step right in.
>> I'm going to do something dumb again.
>> Genuine top quality land certified
merchandise.
All the cash I earn, I save up to buy
myself a rocket powered skateboard.
If that doesn't help, I'll eat my shoe
if I had one.
>> I spent so much. It's okay.
Medium ammo.
Hello.
Second.
Back again.
>> A balanced approach. Somewhat good.
>> I'm broke, bro.
>> [sighs]
>> Watch in correct proportion in
not so much.
One bandage, I guess.
Fine.
I need heals, right?
before you have not
do not freaking die. Do
please.
>> That's all I asked this time. Please.
Ah. [sighs and gasps]
Hello, Ferocious.
Welcome. Welcome.
Hello. Okay.
and I just came to swing by. Ah,
how was your day?
How's your winter holidays going,
ferocious?
Thank you for dropping by. It really
means a lot. Thank you.
What the Where am I?
>> Hope you're close with the season,
Raider. It's a good day for picking
candleberries, but do beware of
frostbite.
>> Uh, chemistry for fire for hours. Holy,
that's crazy.
But I hope you're doing well.
Oh, good luck with exam.
Good luck. Good luck.
All right. Well,
I meant to do this as my head exam my
tips.
Oh, gotcha.
>> Don't shoot.
Okay, I'm doing it.
HEAT. HEAT.
Oh my god, he almost killed me.
Nice.
Okay, nice. Nice, nice, nice, nice,
nice. My god, I
Good luck.
You got this.
Okay, Gucci. We are good, good, good.
Okay, [sighs]
I did not lose any HP. So, uh I defeated
this around what time again? Let me
count it.
Uh I defeat killed it around 26
26 49 of 26 minutes. Okay. calculator
26 - 8
by 18 minutes I'll
go scare
H I don't have anything good. Oh. Oh.
Oh. Nice.
She'll recharge our extra.
I will take that.
Okay, personal best.
Uh, I have to drop something, huh?
I think I can drop this. I think this. I
need that.
Hello there.
>> Hey, Raider.
>> Leaper pulse unit here.
You don't want it. Okay.
>> Thank you.
>> [screaming and groaning]
>> I owe you one.
>> Imagine if I get like a blueprint over
here.
Where is that bandage I had?
Okay.
So this is where I killed the
okay 20. I killed it by six. Okay, we
have to wait uh two more minutes and
then we can try to kill the
thingy.
I would appreciate it if I could guess
get one more bandage.
Ah, thank you very much. Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
That is good.
Like I could kill the thingy and
extract.
I'll be good with that. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah.
I could kill it and extract. That's it.
Okay, an extra. That's good. That will
be good.
Same strategy. Okay.
Okay. One more minute and we start our
leaper hunt.
One more minute. It can spawn over here
or here.
So, you'll have to scout with it
beforehand.
The rocketeers are also there. That's
another headache.
I also need to get the rocketeer thingy
as well. So, I should try to I will not
risk it. I'll just try try. Okay.
Uh 18, right? Okay. It's 18. Okay, it's
officially 18.
Oh, surveys.
Take it easy. Take it slow.
Wait for them to leave.
All right. Good. Good. Good.
So if I killed it from here,
the next spawn,
the next spawn should be that side.
Oh my god, that freaking leaper.
Okay. I do not see the
maybe I think I need a more clear view.
I don't see the leaper.
I do not see the leaper.
I need a
Wait, I don't see the leaper. Where is
the leaper,
bro? I need you.
Wait for myself to get defrosted.
Ah, surveyors.
>> Don't shoot.
Where is the leaper?
Brother, what?
Oh my Lord, holy Lord, Mary, mother of
God.
Where is the leaper?
Brother, what? Brother, what?
No, no, no. This is bad. This is bad.
Where is the stupid reaper?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no. Don't do
this to me. Where is the leaper?
Here or here? No.
>> Oh my god. Where is that?
Who stole my leaper?
>> Don't shoot.
Where the heck is the leaper?
[panting]
Oh my god, this is bad.
Leaper Kun, where did you go?
Why game? Why are you not spawning the
thing when I need it the most?
Where go, man? Where did I go?
I really need you here.
I don't think it is here, man.
Oh [\h__\h]
Oh my god.
I hate this game. I hate this game. I
hate this game. I hate this game. I hate
this game. I hate this game. I hate this
game. I hate this game. I hate this
stupid game, bro.
Freaking hell. What the hell? What the
hell?
Somebody, anybody,
>> please help.
>> 10 minutes to get out of there. I
repeat, 10 minutes.
>> Is that what I hear? That's a freaking
leaper.
I swear to God, this game hates me.
I swear this god, this game hates me.
Please, anybody revive me. Please help.
Please help. Oh, that's Sebastian,
bro. My god, it's dumb.
Why am I like this?
It's not PvP, it's PvE. I'm dying.
Is it me because of me streaming? Why do
I suffer when I stream?
None there,
bro.
Bro,
why do I suffer when I stream?
Just do why.
Just do why. This doesn't make sense.
Why do I suffer when I stream now?
[crying]
I hate this.
I need help, I think.
Oh, well.
I don't know, man.
Don't have anything left on me.
>> He does not know what
I died. It's almost the stupid PC lagged
when the enemies came in. What can I do?
What can I show you?
[crying]
[groaning]
Excuses. Oh,
man.
I lost everything.
I'm poor. I'm broke.
I don't like ice shirt that much. Yeah.
event goes like this. Also, I lost the
blue rarity of a gun, man.
I bought it for 30,000 space dollars and
I lost it. I lost this one.
Life hates me.
And I go free load out.
I have to buy ammo. I don't have I do
not have ammo.
Got your eye on something
>> used for guns with some proper zip to
them. Should work great on armor.
>> When life is hard,
you must also be hard. [laughter]
>> It's yours.
>> I'll try.
I'll try. Doohoo.
I had so many chances and I
I support every one of them.
That's the sad part. Honestly,
I don't want to use these big boys. I
have to use this on the other one
for the other big boys. I'm suffering on
the easiest one. I mean, it's not
easiest, but
you know. You know,
skill is to deny. Oh, it's the clankers.
Is it okay to even use that word? I
Every streamer I watch, our creator
stream, they use the word clanker. The
metal robots.
the stupid clankers, man. Why the hex
this like imagine I'm suffering with PVE
this game everyone PVEs
and I'm glad I'm getting friendly
lobbies but
man I'm suffering if I'm like this I'll
going to be super suffering in PVP
[laughter] oh my god
[sighs]
that'll be Crazy.
I'm going to use my everything.
That's all I can do.
>> Hey, always nice to see a friendly face.
What do you need?
I'm going to zero.
Can't buy those.
>> Funny thing about gadgets, half the
funds figuring out what they actually
do.
>> Ah, my money.
My money is going a bit.
Okay.
Call snap. H I don't want to do damn
man. Damn is more
pain.
I don't I have to use the traitor for
the other stuff now.
>> What's the damage?
>> Take it. Use it. And try not to bleed on
it.
>> Yeah.
>> To the coffer it goes.
>> I'll try not to bleed.
Why did I buy extra shield when I
already had B token taken shields? Ah,
dumb dumb
don't take. Ah, fine. I'll take one that
um
deadline just in case. You never know
what can happen. Fine, I'm going in. I
swear if I die to this, I'm I'm I'm
ending stream.
[laughter] No, I I'll I'll not end
stream. I'll just give up on it.
Uh we have to uh we have to make 100,000
100,000
money back now. We'll I'll just stop
doing this.
And maybe
I don't know. Or I could just do the
other bosses, the other clankish. Big
Clankish.
I can twoot him with the Oh, to the wolf
pack grenade.
Yeah.
Okay, let's go.
I mean, I can just kill uh like Ah, my
species stuff is struggling. Please
don't struggle.
Why is it struggling? I don't get it.
Brother, what?
Uh,
okay. It's a fresh trade.
Find the leaper.
Kill and extract. That's it.
That's all I have to do.
Look for the sound queue.
I hear people.
Okay. So, it's not near the dam.
If it's not here, it will be probably
here.
I don't hear sounds. Okay.
Uh, if it's not here, then it's here. I
don't see it anywhere here.
Don't shoot.
>> Oh my god, this guy's high rocking big
boy guns. Oh my god, he's rocking big
boy guns.
Damn. Good luck, Ray. Good luck, Raider.
Did I hear? Oh, I hear something.
Okay, it's not here.
Wait, I Oh my god, someone died.
Oh my god.
This is not how I ever wanted to act.
[\h__\h] this game. [\h__\h] this game. [\h__\h]
this game.
[\h__\h] this game.
Why?
Boy,
[crying]
[gasps]
I think I need a mate. Solos is
just not working.
>> Hello.
>> Okay.
[laughter]
We died, bro.
I hate life
as we know it.
Life sucks. He's talking.
[laughter]
>> I'm sorry.
>> I hate everything.
Man,
why is it always the rocketeer?
At least my dead my deadline is there.
[laughter]
At least my deadline is there.
And
sucks.
It really sucks.
One down, you take less damage. I need
to take turtle coal now. So, um
[sighs]
I lost everything, man.
Well, that means we got to go freak it.
We're going freak it.
Or I can try to do the challenges and
get all the
get all the workshop levels up.
That's one thing I could do. Yep.
like especially Bastion and everything
now.
We can just do that.
Go in naked and then Bastion kill it
probably.
I could do that.
Bombeteer, Bastion, Rocketeer, Survey,
Evolve, Sentinel.
I think I need the Rocketeer now.
Um
We'll do a free cut.
>> I need to bring back money.
I'll I'll go downstairs and drink my
tea.
Okay.
I'll go downstairs and drink my tea. I
need to do that.
Reload. Okay.
Okay. I'll be back. Give me a minute.
So
What the?
>> Uh,
what the
Okay, I'll be back. One second. Okay.
Uh,
where is the BRB thingy?
>> Where are we?
Let me just get I'll be back. Okay.
A few minutes. Okay.
All disruptions caused by unexplained
power outages are now part of the adapt.
at the end of the line.
Hallelujah.
Yeah,
Night soup looks the same, but the
cook's wear is different.
Thank you for that money.
to check the store.
The family temporarily
detail.
Somebody take a smiling face to the
animal and help us somehow.
Okay, I'm back.
Ah,
yeah. Freak it.
Oh boy.
Apparently, I couldn't find my tea. I
just ate drank something.
I came back.
Oh, boy. [laughter]
>> So, we are in a loss. We need to make
some money
and I'll stream till 8. Okay.
I only stream till 8 today.
Not bad.
I hate it.
>> Hey, Apollo here. Did you bring those
grenades, Raider? My new designs look
great on paper, but I'll need someone to
chuck them at some machines to know
anything for sure.
>> It's a fresh rate. Um,
I don't know where I am.
No distract.
I'm here.
>> Okay, there's one, two.
>> Let's move to that location.
Hey, don't shoot.
>> OKAY,
the game is lagging so much.
I could find some loot.
I'm bad.
Was
that a horn?
Why is the bomb chair on top?
Yeah, it is
Heat. Heat.
I want to kill it.
Oh [\h__\h]
I hate you. I hate you. I just want to
let you know that I hate you
blanker.
I don't have I do not have heavy hitting
boys.
I do not have any heavy hitting
items which I could use.
Who's fighting?
Like this is a good spot to kill it
honestly,
but ah
only if I had good stuff
or me. I could have just killed the
bastion
bomber right now.
I would have been rich, man.
If I'm lucky to get like a grenade
somehow, I'm I'll be so happy.
Smoke grenade.
I need to get out of here.
I see a player.
White nice stuff.
I really hate it when my PC lags so
much.
Yeah. doing the good stuff.
I'll take the spring.
Oh, nice.
>> Hello.
>> Don't shoot.
I have a friend.
>> HEY
HEAT. HEAT.
Oh my god. I'm dead. I'm dead. I'm dead.
I'm dead.
Hey, don't shoot.
Don't shoot.
COME ON. Thank you.
I got two of them.
Head
home at the northern station.
OKAY, WE need to extract right now.
We need an extra right now and reset. I
have 27k worth of stuff.
>> Hey, don't shoot.
Hello.
Team up. Don't shoot.
on the platform. Opening door should
stand by.
Okay, that was a good extract. Holy
lord. Nice.
Nice. Oh my god, that was nice. Oh my
god.
Got a good I I I stole the van, by the
way.
I stole that.
The guy just dropped it. I yined it and
just left the scene.
Welcome back, feller.
We did not make much money.
It goes dark.
It usually comes back.
I can't die.
Barricade cat.
Broer.
>> Oh, they gave me a snap hook
and a guitar. Oh,
and the level
epic argument, too. Oh.
[snorts]
Nice.
Whether it's love, work, or checked.
I got um
matri here on here.
We could free load out go for the
matriarch.
How about that?
So I need six uh five uh no three four
more cells
then my refinery is max level.
I just need
bastion cell as well.
>> Wow.
Spaceport has a nitrate.
I want to go
I'm just going to use
weapons I already have.
The thing is I can't afford guns or
anything. So I'll just go for a look
load out.
Maybe I'll I can just go to Stella,
get some stuff from Stella then extract
maybe.
Yeah, that would be the best choice.
[snorts]
Pab
H.
This is TENWEN SPEAKING. REMEMBER,
YOU'RE not there to take in the sights.
I'll need the details from you later.
I got on top, wasn't it?
Where?
Bro, there's nothing here.
Give me something.
Oh, nice. I needed this.
Hey, Raider.
Why am I picking up oil
for no reason?
Heat. Heat.
M.
I need good stuff. I do not have any
good stuff.
LET'S TAKE THAT METRO ENTRANCE. HEAD
home at the seat vault air shaft.
Ah, this looted.
Everything is looted.
Oh my god.
I don't want to deal with that.
I do not want to deal with that.
Every single
>> Don't shoot
>> thing has looted.
>> HEY
No good stuff.
An arc orbiter is on route. The safe
window is closing. You have 10 minutes
to return to Sparanza. I repeat, 10
minutes.
>> Yeah, I should extract.
>> Head home at the Loading Bay Metro.
Don't shoot.
>> Let's use that metro entrance.
>> Are they killing each other?
Super
heat.
Oh my lord. I'm dead. I am dead.
Brother, I'm dead.
>> Let's take that metro entrance.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Just
go. Just go. Just go score.
I called it right. I called it right.
Ah, there was a loot,
brother. [groaning]
brother. Why? There's two dead bodies,
bro.
I could have gooped hard.
I could have gooped.
I could have goofped, man.
I'm sorry.
I needed the rushed gear.
I could have gooped
if I had more health.
That is
could have gooped him more.
Uh
there's
>> mine
my red. We need some stuff.
I feel like at times like this, I feel
like I need like a teammate
>> cuz I'm dying a lot in this game.
>> I am dying a lot.
Oh,
Have your eyes
>> loot is ripe for the picking while most
of Toledo is asleep though my suppliers
say that ark is twice as vigilant after
sunset
containers.
I'll take the spring right near the
spring.
Light looks a bit different here.
The thing is that when you have a
if you're in NA servers and stuff,
people will be PvPing hard.
It's going to be hectic.
and hard
Space for container Borax here.
There are people.
As long as I don't get shot in the back,
I'm fine.
Almost got caught in fire, but it's
okay.
nothing much.
I love they are giving me grenades now.
When I wanted it, you never gave me.
Oh my god. Nice.
Hey, don't shoot.
I could try going to control tower.
Maybe
maybe I'll find some luck. Maybe. Not
sure.
I mean, that man is nice and all, but
not much.
I don't get much.
>> HEY, DON'T SHOOT.
I THINK THE GUY is downstairs.
If I really needed money, I could just
go to commercial area and just get some
loot, right?
How far is the I should
loot it.
Extended
mag, huh?
All the good stuff got looted.
You're calling me.
Oh my god.
Um,
okay.
I needed that. So,
I need this.
Yeah, it should be best if I could reset
it right now
cuz I don't want to
Let's head home at the south elevator.
>> I could just reset.
ENEMY
STAND.
>> HEY, DON'T SHOOT. PROCEED
to elevate.
Thank you.
People are nice.
Let's go
kill them. No, I can't PVP. I'll be put
in a PvP lobby. I don't want to PvP.
I'll die though. I'm already dying to
arc and I I almost rage quit today.
[laughter]
I almost rage quit it today. It was
crazy.
Like um two hour 1 hour ago. Two hour
ago. Yeah. 1 hour ago. I was ra
quitting, man.
I was raised up. I couldn't
It was too much.
I didn't make money.
Well,
really [laughter]
more.
I need two more.
Oh, one more. Yeah. Our
passengers are closing.
Uh, they throw their controls out. Yeah,
I never did that.
That's crazy.
Okay, that's a really light free setup,
I believe.
back online.
Let's go.
I said I'll stream till one more hour.
No.
Yeah,
I'll have to wrap up soon. I am having
headache. Wa! No,
but it's okay.
Okay, we load up this place.
>> Let's go to the warehouse.
I think I have to go upstairs.
Nice. Nice.
There's this.
Okay. Next is fuel depot.
Nothing here.
Industrial battery spring.
Go to the arrival building.
>> Could go there.
Need to check the
lockers
for something.
Breach this.
Never know if I can get like a
blueprint. You never know.
Okay. I haven't seen the battery
and no one looted this area.
There's already people here.
>> Hello.
>> Don't shoot.
Of
course they all they all looted this.
I'll take the wine board though.
HELLO.
>> THANKS.
ANTISEPTIC.
I needed that.
>> Don't shoot.
Cracked laboratory resonance.
I mean, there's nothing much here.
>> Hey, team up. HEY,
they already looted this as well.
Damn,
these guys are so quick. Oh, there isn't
the best one. Oh, never mind.
>> Let's go to the launch towers.
Did someone die?
I really, really, really wish to take
down a hornet.
He saw me.
Elevator.
Okay,
nice.
I love them much.
Give me stuff.
Seeker grenade. I don't need it.
Hey.
Hey there.
I don't I have a grenade.
Just 24 ammo. I don't think I should
risk it.
Would have been good if I could just
kill it, you know.
Would have been super good.
Okay. Should I extract or should I
search for more stuff for me? I'm kind
of filled up right now.
I could actually
>> Hey. Hello. Don't shoot.
Pewatch.
Stand by.
Let's begin.
Go ahead. The elevator is ready.
[groaning]
>> Okay,
that was a good one. We got like
something.
We got a few stuff. That is nice.
Huh?
Come on.
I need the spring. Yep.
Uh uh.
Okay.
Okay, we going again.
I got to hit the good places.
I feel like I'm super broke. I need to
gather materials now.
Like if I'm finding ammo and stuff now,
I have to bring it back home.
I feel like
cuz I'm running out of them.
So, what are you?
Uh, hello penguin. I just saw your
message.
Don't don't don't be here. Uh just run
the rocket assembly.
>> Go to the rocket assembly.
No,
service.
Oh, nice. Nice.
Hello.
Yeah, it's all. No worries. No worries.
All it's all good.
How was your Christmas? It was as usual.
Nothing much.
Just a normal day,
that's all.
My Christmas was just normal.
Yeah,
>> let's move to that location. Go to the
departure building.
>> How was your Christmas?
>> Hey, don't shoot. OKAY.
I don't celebrate Christmas.
Hi. But still, what did you do there?
Like, did you go to the malls or
something to see how others celebrate
Christmas?
Sleep and eat.
So then
I also did that
during Christmas. I slept and ate.
I went to the nature. Oh, that's nice.
Nice.
How are you? I enjoyed it. I'm doing
good.
I'm doing good.
>> Oh my god. Why are you shooting?
>> Don't shoot. Don't shoot. Don't shoot.
They're They're peving, bro.
>> Don't shoot.
Should I risk it?
I'm 19k.
Are you real, Joey? I am real.
Hey, don't shoot. Hey, don't shoot.
Hey, don't shoot.
>> What the heck, bro?
Look up. Danger. Danger up there.
>> HEY, DON'T SHOOT. DON'T SHOOT.
>> Want to go together?
>> Don't shoot.
My bad.
>> GG.
[\h__\h]
Why did I risk it when there was PvP? I
had a a one tapping gun.
Bro, the guy was PvPing. Oh, no. PvE
lobby. Friendly lobby. What? I mean, uh,
I shouldn't be surprised people in this
game,
man.
Man,
I like the purple stuff. Uh,
I just need firing code.
Ventor.
Those guys were PVPing. [singing]
I hate it.
I could free load out this
and go to damn
the matria,
but you need a good amount of blueprints
and stuff. I'm not lucky with the blue
guns.
That's the thing.
>> I'm not that lucky actually.
Okay, it's 7:30.
I want to stream more but honestly
speaking because I because this game is
too much for my PC. No.
A part of me is like should I just play
it off stream or something?
>> Watch your backs, Raiders. The matriarch
is in. Go to the testing area. Keep your
wits about you if you decide to go
anywhere near and all nearby children.
Well, grenade.
O, that hurt.
All right.
This is not loaded, which is nice.
Give me some good stuff.
There's nice
and this
someone just died.
Okay, this is also not loaded.
A lot of adrenaline shots.
Oh, this is a medical container place.
That's why.
I may have a chance to
uh see.
Nope.
>> Okay, we got to go.
>> Let's go to research and administration.
Oh yeah.
That was the stupidest thing I could
ever do in my life.
Jocklex, what is up with you?
Okay. Go go go go go go go go go go go
go go go.
Oh, the sentinel is there.
There we go.
DON'T SHOOT.
OKAY, NO ONE'S HERE.
HEY, don't shoot.
It's already searched.
I thought that was a blueprint.
Game stop lagging. What the heck?
The guy
came loaded
and went.
Hey, don't shoot.
Wow.
I came here, looted, and just scraddled
like nothing.
Uh, he came here, too. Oh my god.
Leave something for the rest of us. Come
on.
I saw a humidifier. I needed that.
I saw a human medifier.
I'll need this. I need this. I need
this. I need this. Ah, I'll
boy. Uh,
maybe this. Baby
came here.
Okay, we have nothing left.
The guy who came here
already full clean this
There's nothing here anyway.
I think I have a feeling that he got all
the goop.
I need this internal core. And I'm going
to extract
Yes,
I will replace it with
uh this
what? Just one thing.
That's it.
Okay, I have to extract
>> home at the Red Lake Balcony lift.
HEAT. HEAT.
I should not distract her.
Oh my lord. Holy m of god.
Why
>> is
>> [\h__\h] helling?
10 minutes to get out of there. I
repeat, 10 minutes.
Elevator up.
Go ahead. The elevator is ready.
>> Okay. Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go,
go.
Oh my lord.
I for a second I was worried that I did
not open the
extract. Call for the extract.
Oh, thank God.
Like since I'm not doing PvP in this
game. No. And like I'm playing it scary
like playing it slow and as if I'm
scared and stuff.
Yeah. Like when I watch other streamers
who play this game though, they don't
worry about the clankers. They worry
about the PV players.
Clan guns are easy for them to kill.
Yeah, my game is freezing. I think it's
time for me to wrap up.
Compensator.
Okay, final thing.
Yay. Salary.
Oh,
wow.
This is not enough.
102.
This is enough.
I mean, I do not mind if I give you like
paper code, I guess.
This is crazy. I need to give a 1
million worth of items.
Oh boy.
Crazy, man.
Clear to the ground.
Oh my god.
Can settle this.
I can just dump some stuff here. No,
which I don't need.
Why is it go pump?
disconnect.
I can treat this as a waste bin. Maybe
M.
>> Oh,
stuff. If I don't need will be these.
Now
I can like clear up my
storage.
I will not give you my bobcat.
Uh, no. Uh, mister.
>> Good to see you.
>> Why the Oh my god. Why did I do that?
Another fine choice. Clearly you have
taste.
>> See, this is why I like you.
I kind of want to sell something.
Someone's Of course.
Oh god, this should be enough.
Okay, we can wrap it up. It's going to
be eight. Yeah, I'll wrap it up over
wrap it up.
>> We failed a lot of missions today. We
died a lot.
or something.
I lost three times
trying to do this challenge.
I could have won,
but well,
but it is what it is. It's okay.
Okay,
let me switch.
All right.
All right. We can wrap it up for
tonight. It was really fun.
Hope you guys also enjoyed it. Thank you
to those who came by and sticked around
till the end. It really, really, really
means a lot.
Thank you.
Okay, let me prepare the redirect.
Oh, thank you to all who came by today.
I will be
um raiding you to my
always on channel. But yeah, thank you
for today. It was really fun to talk.
I'll see you guys tomorrow. Maybe. Yeah,
tomorrow I'll try to stream. Yep.
Tomorrow I'll try to stream stream. The
thing is I would love to stream this
game. It's just that I've been so
unlucky when I stream this game. And
I've been lucky when I do not stream
this game. Is that normal? That is
definitely not normal. Dio,
I can assure you that is definitely not
normal. Anyhow, we'll wrap it up here.
Thank you to all who were there. Thank
you. Really means a lot. Have a good
one. Have a great night, everyone.
And bye-bye.
Good night. Good night. Good night. Good
night.
Thank you for coming. Bye.
See you tomorrow.